На выпелнение контролную работу ушло 9 часов 11 до 19:00


added button to Index View  -- 10 мин

change code to LoanBook in Controller -- 1 часов 5 мин

added new Action to BookController and chanage code View, and added BookLoanViewModel added new migrations -- 2 часов

added AccountController and Login, Register -- 1 30 часов


added new Model Category and added Controller, View and added migrations  --- 1 час 5 мин

added Services and ViewModel, changes View Book  -- 1 час 15 мин

added BookController  -- 15 мин

added migrations and connection database -- 5мин

added new Model Book and LibraryContext, and connection database -- 15 мин

created project ControlWork7  -- 5мин
